- Good morning.
Here ye, here ye, 10 minutes to go
till Van Dort's wedding rehearsal.
Watch it!
It's a beautiful day.
It's a rather nice day.
A day for a glorious wedding.
A rehearsal, my dear
To be perfectly clear.
A rehearsal
for a glorious wedding.
Assuming nothing happens
That we don't really know.
That nothing unexpected
Interferes with the show.
And that's why everything
Every last little thing.
Every single, tiny, microscopic
Little thing must go.
- According to plan.
- Our son will be married.
- Our family carried.
Elevated to the heights
of society.
- To the costume balls.
- In the hallowed halls.
Rubbing elbows with the finest.
Having crumpets
with Her Highness.
We'll be there, we'll be seen
Having tea with the queen.
We'll forget everything
That we've ever, ever been.
- Blimey! It's my dress is caught.
- Begging your pardon, ma'am.
- Come on, dear.
- It's not me. It's my dress.
Where is Victor?
We might be late.
Fish merchants.
- It's a terrible day.
- Now, don't be that way.
It's a terrible day
for a wedding.
It's a sad, sad state
of affairs we're in.
That has led to this
ominous wedding.
How could our family
have come to this?
To marry off our daughter
To the nouveau riche.
- They're so common.
- So coarse.
- Oh, it couldn't be worse.
- Couldn't be worse? I disagree.
They could be land-rich,
Bankrupt aristocracy.
Without a penny to their name.
Just like you and me.
Oh, dear.
And that's why everything
Every last little thing.
Every single, tiny, microscopic
Little thing must go.
- According to plan.
- Our daughter will wed.
- Our family led.
From the depths
of deepest poverty.
- To the noble realm.
- Of our ancestry.
And who would have guessed
In a million years.
- That our daughter with a face.
- Of an otter in disgrace.
Would provide our ticket
To a rightful place.
Oh, Hildegarde.
What if Victor and I don't
like each other?
As if that has anything
to do with marriage.
Do you suppose your father
and I like each other?
Surely you must a little?
- Of course not.
Get those corsets
laced properly.
I can hear you speak
without gasping.
You've certainly hooked
a winner this time, Victor.
- Now, all you have to do is reel her in.
- I'm already reeling, Mother.
Shouldn't Victoria Everglot be
marrying a lord or something?
Oh, nonsense! We're every bit
as good as the Everglots.
I always knew I deserved better
than a fish merchant's life.
But I've never
even spoken to her.
Well, at least we have
that in our favor.
Mayhew!
Silence that blasted coughing.
Marriage is a partnership,
a little tit for tat.
You'd think a lifetime
watching us...
Might have taught her that.
- Might have taught her that.
- Everything must be perfect.
Perfect That's why everything.
Every last little thing.
Every single, tiny, microscopic
Little thing must go.
According to plan.
Look at the way you're standing.
You look like you got
rickets or something...
Oh!
Oh, my goodness. Oh, such grandeur!
Such impeccable taste!
- Oh, beautiful, innit?
- Hmph.
It's not as big
as our place, dear.
- Bit shabby really, isn't it?
- Shut up.
Lord and Lady Everglot...
Mr. and Mrs. Van Dort.
Why, you must be Miss Victoria.
Yes, I must say, you don't look
a day over 20. No. Oh, yes.
Smile, darling, smile.
Well, hello. What a pleasure.
Welcome to our home.
Oh, thank you.
We'll be taking tea
in the west drawing room.
Oh, do come this way,
it's just through there.
Oh, I love what you've done with the place.
Who is your decorator?
Nice tiles, shame
about the drapes.
Oh, my husband says such foolish things.
Ignore him.
Oh, yes, it's usually best.
- Do forgive me.
- You play beautifully.
I... I... I do apologize, Miss Everglot.
How rude of me to... Well...
Excuse me.
Mother won't let
me near the piano.
Music is improper
for a young lady.
Too passionate, she says.
If I may ask, Miss Everglot...
where is your chaperon?
Perhaps, in... In view
of the circumstances...
you could call me Victoria.
Yes, of course. Well...
- Victoria...
- Yes, Victor.
Tomorrow, we are to be m...
M... M...
- Married.
- Yes. Ha. Married.
Since I was a child, I've...
I've dreamt of my wedding day.
I always hoped to find someone
I was deeply in love with.
Someone to spend the rest
of my life with.
- Silly, isn't it?
- Yes, silly. Ha.
No. No, not at all, no.
Oh! Oh, dear.
I'm sorry.
What impropriety is this?
You shouldn't be alone together.
Here it is, one minute before 5,
and you're not at the rehearsal.
Pastor Galswells is waiting.
Come at once.
Master Van Dort, from the beginning.
Again.
"With this hand,
I will lift your sorrows."
Your cup will never empty,
for I will be your wine.
With this candle, I will light
your way in darkness.
"With this ring, I ask
you to be mine."
- Let's try it again.
- Yes. Yes, sir.
With this candle...
This candle...
This candle.
Shall I get up there
and do it for him?
Don't get all aflutter, dear.
With this candle...
Continue!
Get the door, Emil.
Let's just pick it
up at the candle bit.
A Lord Barkis, sir.
I haven't a head for dates.
Apparently, I'm a day
early for the ceremony.
- Is he from your side of the family?
- I can't recall.
Emil, a seat for Lord Barkis.
Do carry on.
Let's try it again, shall
we, Master Van Dort?
- Yes. Yes, sir. Certainly.
- Right.
Right. Oh, right!
- With this... this...
- Hand.
With this hand...
I... With...
Three steps, three!
Can you not count? Do you not wish
to be married, Master Van Dort?
- No! No.
- You do not?
No! I meant, no, I do not
not wish to be married.
That is, I want very much to...
Ow!
Pay attention! Have you
even remembered to bring the ring?
The ring? Yes. Of course.
Dropping the ring.
Oh, no, he's dropped the ring!
- This boy doesn't want to get married.
- How disgraceful!
Excuse me. Got it!
Out of the way, you ninny.
Oh, dear! Oh, my! Giddy on,
a woman on fire! Help! Emergency!
- Oh, I hope it doesn't stain.
- Stop fanning it, you fool.
- Get a bucket, get a bucket.
- I'm on my way, dear. Yes. Oh, dear!
Enough! This wedding cannot take
place until he is properly prepared.
Young man, learn your vows.
Well, he's quite
the catch, isn't he?
Oh, Victoria.
She must think I'm such a fool.
This day couldn't get any worse.
TOWN CRIER Hear ye, hear ye!
Rehearsal in ruins as Van
Dort boy causes chaos!
Fishy fiancé could be canned!
Everglots all fired up as Van
Dort disaster ruins rehearsal!
It really shouldn't be
all that difficult.
It's just a few simple vows.
With this hand,
I will take your wine.
No.
With this hand...
I will cup your...
Oh, goodness, no.
With this...
With this candle, I will...
I will...
I will set your mother on fire.
Oh, it's no use.
With this hand,
I will lift your sorrows.
Your cup will never empty,
for I will be your wine.
Ah, Mrs. Everglot.
You look ravishing this evening.
What's that, Mr. Everglot? Call you "Dad"?
If you insist, sir.
With this candle, I will light
your way in darkness.
With this ring...
I ask you to be mine.
I do.
You may kiss the bride.
- A new arrival.
- He must've fainted.
- Are you all right?
- What...? What happened?
By Jove, man. Looks like we've got
ourselves a breather.
- Does he have a dead brother?
- He's still soft.
A toast, then.
To the newlyweds.
Newlyweds?
Oh, in the woods, you said
your vows so perfectly.
I did?
I did.
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up!
Bonjour!
Coming through, coming through.
My name is Paul, I am
the head waiter.
I will be creating
your wedding feast.
Wedding feast!
I'm salivating.
Maggots.
- Oh!
- Hey!
Keep away!
I've got a... I've got a dwarf.
And I'm not afraid to use him.
I want some questions. Now!
- Answers. I think you mean "answers."
- Thank you, yes, answers.
I need answers. What's going on here?
Where am I?
Who are you?
Well, that's kind
of a long story.
What a story it is.
A tragic tale
of romance, passion...
and murder most foul.
- This is gonna be good.
- Oh!
Hit it, boys.
Hey, give me a listen
You corpses of cheer.
At least those of you
Who still got an ear.
I'll tell you a story
Make a skeleton cry.
Of our own jubiliciously
Lovely Corpse Bride.
Die, die, we all pass away.
But don't wear a frown
Because it's really okay.
You might try and hide And
you might try and pray.
But we all end up The
remains of the day.
That's right.
Well, our girl was a beauty
Known for miles around.
When a mysterious
stranger Came into town.
He was plenty good-looking
But down on his cash.
And our poor little baby
She fell hard and fast.
When her daddy said no
She just couldn't cope.
So our lovers came
up With a plan to elope.
Die, die, we all pass away.
But don't wear a frown
Because it's really okay.
You might try and hide And
you might try and pray.
But we all end up The
remains of the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
That's right.
Ah, okay. Oh, yeah.
Come on, boys, pick it up.
Yeah. Like it.
Okay, Chancy, take it.
Yeah. Whoo!
Yeah!
That's nice.
So they conjured up a plan
To meet late at night.
They told not a soul Kept
the whole thing tight.
Now, her mother's wedding
dress Fit like a glove.
You don't need much When
you're really in love.
Except for a few things
Or so I'm told.
Like the family jewels
And a satchel of gold.
Then next to the graveyard
By the old oak tree.
On a dark, foggy night
At a quarter to 3.
She was ready to go
But where was he?
And then?
- She waited.
- And then?
- There in the shadows, was it her man?
- Her little heart beat so loud.
- And then?
And then, baby,
everything went black.
Now, when she opened her
eyes She was dead as dust.
Her jewels were missing
And her heart was bust.
So she made a vow Lying
under that tree.
That she'd wait for her true
love To come set her free.
Always waiting for someone
To ask for her hand.
Then out of the blue Comes
this groovy young man.
Who vows forever
To be by her side.
And that's the story
Of our Corpse Bride.
Die, die, we all pass away.
But don't wear a frown,
Because it's really okay.
You might try and hide And
you might try and pray.
But we all end up The
remains of the day.
Yeah.
Victoria, come away
from the window.
Oh, I'm sure he'll be
back shortly.
He's terrified of the dark.
In fact, when he was a boy...
he used to wet his combinations
regularly, didn't he, William?
Enter.
Ah, Lord Barkis. I trust
the room is to your liking.
Thank you, you
are a most gracious hostess.
Which is why it pains me to be
the bearer of such bad news.
Would you care to repeat
tonight's headline for us?
Hear ye, hear ye!
Victor Van Dort seen this night on the bridge
in the arms of a mystery woman!
The dark-haired temptress and Master
Van Dort slipped away into the night!
And now, the weather.
Scattered showers...
Enough!
That will be all.
Mystery woman? He doesn't
even know any women!
Or so you thought.
Do call for me if you
need my assistance...
in any way.
Good heavens, Finis,
what should we do?
Fetch me musket.
William, do something.
The town crier probably
just had a slow news day.
You know how it is, you need
a little something to cry about.
Regardless, we are one groom
short for the wedding tomorrow.
Not to mention the financial
implications.
A most scandalous
embarrassment for us all.
Oh, give us a chance to find
him, we beg of you.
- Just give us until dawn.
- Very well. Till dawn.
Victor, darling, where are you?
If you ask me, your boyfriend
is kind of jumpy.
He's not my boyfriend,
he's my husband.
Victor, where have you gone?
I'll keep an eye out for him.
Victor?
There he goes, there he goes!
He's... He's getting away!
Quick, quick, after him!
Victor.
Thank you.
Victor!
Where are you?
Victor?
Where have you gone?
Married, huh? I'm a widow.
Oh, how rude. He went that way!
Victor.
Victor, darling.
Please. There's been a mistake.
I'm not dead.
Oh!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Thank you.
Victor.
- Dead end.
- Victor!
Hello!
Could have used
the stairs, silly.
Isn't the view beautiful?
It takes my breath away.
Well, it would if I had any.
Isn't it romantic?
Look, I am terribly sorry
about what's happened to you...
and I'd like to help,
but I really need to get home.
- This is your home now.
- But I don't even know your name.
Well, that's a great way
to start a marriage.
Shut up!
- It's Emily.
- Emily.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I have something for you.
It's a wedding present.
Thank you.
Scraps?
Scraps!
My dog, Scraps!
Oh, Scraps, what a good boy.
I knew you'd be
happy to see him.
Who's my good boy? Sit.
Sit, Scraps, sit.
Good boy, Scraps. Roll over.
Roll over.
Good boy, Scraps. Play dead.
Sorry.
Oh, what a cutie.
You should have
seen him with fur.
Mother never approved of Scraps
jumping up like this.
But then again, she never
approved of anything.
Do you think she would have
approved of me?
You're lucky you'll never
have to meet her.
Well, actually...
now that you mention it,
I think you should.
In fact, since we're,
you know...
married, you should
definitely meet her.
And my father too. We should
go and see them right now.
What a fantastic idea!
Where are they buried?
Oh.
- What? What is it?
- They're not from around here.
Where are they?
Oh, they're still alive.
- I'm afraid so.
- Well, that is a problem.
What's that, Scraps?
Oh, no, we couldn't possibly.
- Oh, well, if you put it like that.
- What?
Elder Gutknecht.
Shh, Scraps.
Elder Gutknecht...
are you there?
Hello? Is anyone home?
Hello?
There you are!
Oh, my dear. There you are.
I've brought my husband, Victor.
What's that? Husband?
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
We need to go up. Upstairs?
To visit the land of the living.
Land of the living?
Oh, my dear.
Please, Elder Gutknecht.
Now, why go up there, when people
are dying to get down here?
Sir, I beg you to help.
It means so much to me...
- Us.
- I don't know, it's just not natural.
Please, Elder Gutknecht.
Surely there must be
something you can do.
Hmm.
Let me see what I can do.
Where did I put that book?
I left it here somewhere.
Ah, there's the one.
Umm...
I have it.
A Ukrainian haunting spell.
Just the thing for these quick trips.
So glad you thought of this.
Me too.
Ah.
Now, then...
Where were we?
- The Ukrainian haunting spell?
- Aha.
Ah, here we have it. Ready?
Just remember, when you want
to come back, say "Hopscotch."
- Hopscotch?
- That's it.
I spent so long
in the darkness...
I'd almost forgotten
how beautiful the moonlight is.
Psst. Hey, I think you
dropped something.
Hold on, hold on.
I think I should prepare Mother
and Father for the big news.
I'll go ahead and you...
wait here.
- Perfect.
- I won't be long.
Stay right here.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
No peeking.
If ever I see
that Van Dort boy...
I'll strangle him
with my bare hands.
Your hands are too fat,
and his neck is too thin.
You'll have to use a rope.
This is the voice of your conscience.
Listen to what I say.
I have a bad feeling about that boy.
You know he is no...
Go chew someone
else's ear for a while.
Victor has gone to see
his parents, just like he said.
If I hadn't just been sitting in it,
I would say that you had lost your mind!
I'm sure he has a perfectly
good reason for taking so long.
I am sure he does.
Why don't you go ask him?
All right, I will.
After all, he couldn't get
far with those cold feet.
- Victoria.
- Victor? I'm so happy to see you.
Come by the fire. Where have you been?
Are you all right?
I... I...
Oh, dear.
You're as cold as death.
What's happened to you?
Your coat.
Victoria, I confess.
This morning I was terrified
of marriage.
But then, on meeting you, I felt
I should be with you always...
and that our wedding could
not come soon enough.
Oh!
Victor, I feel the same.
Victoria, I se... I se...
I seem to find myself married.
And you should know
it's unexpected.
My darling, I just
wanted to meet...
Darling? Who's this?
- Who is she?
- I'm his wife.
- Victor?
- Victoria, wait. You don't understand.
She's dead. Look.
Hopscotch.
No! No!
Victoria!
You lied to me!
Just to get back
to that other woman.
Don't you understand?
You're the other woman.
No! You're married to me.
She's the other woman.
She's got a point.
And I thought... I thought
this was all going so well.
Look, I'm sorry, but...
this just can't work.
Why not?
It's my eye, isn't it?
No. Your eye is...
lovely.
Listen, under different
circumstances, well, who knows?
But we're just too different.
I mean, you're dead.
You should've thought about that before you
asked me to marry you.
Why can't you understand? It was a mistake.
I would never marry you.
Roses for eternal love.
Lilies for sweetness.
Baby's breath.
Why so blue?
Maybe he's right.
Maybe we are too different.
Maybe he should have
his head examined.
I could do it.
Or perhaps he does belong with her.
Little Miss Living.
With her rosy cheeks
and beating heart.
Oh, those girls are 10 a penny.
You've got so much more.
You've got... You've got...
You've got a wonderful
personality.
What does that wispy little brat
have That you don't have double?
She can't hold a candle To
the beauty of your smile.
How about a pulse?
Overrated by a mile.
- Overvalued.
- Overblown.
If he only knew The
you that we know.
And that silly little creature
Isn't wearing his ring.
And she doesn't play
piano Or dance, or sing.
No, she doesn't compare.
- But she still breathes air.
- Who cares?
- Unimportant.
- Overrated.
- Overblown.
- If only he could see.
How special you can be.
If he only knew The
you that we know.
If I touch a burning
candle I can feel no pain.
If you cut me with a knife
It's still the same.
And I know her heart is beating.
And I know that I am dead.
Yet the pain here that I feel.
Try and tell me it's not real.
And it seems that I still
have A tear to shed.
The sole redeeming feature
From that little creature.
Is that she's alive.
- Overrated.
- Overblown.
Everybody knows That's just
a temporary state.
Which is cured very quickly
When we meet our fate.
- Who cares?
- Unimportant.
- Overrated.
- Overblown.
If only he could see How
special you can be.
If he only knew The
you that we know.
If I touch a burning
candle I can feel no pain.
In the ice or in the sun
It's all the same.
Yet I feel my heart is aching.
Though it doesn't
beat, it's breaking.
And the pain here that I feel.
Try and tell me it's not real.
I know that I am dead.
Yet it seems that I still
have Some tears to shed.
It's true, Mother!
Victor is married
to a dead woman.
I saw her. A corpse!
Standing right here with Victor.
Victor was in your room?
I have to help him.
The scandal!
Come sit in your chair, dearie.
You're shaking like a leaf.
Let Hilde fetch you a blanket.
Fetch her a straitjacket!
She's completely mad!
Come, Hildegarde.
Finis, come to bed at once.
Oh!
What in heaven's name?
Who could that be at this hour?
Miss Everglot.
What are you doing here? You should
be at home, prostrate with grief.
Pastor Galswells, I have
to ask you something.
- This is most irregular.
- Please, I beg of you.
You are the only one in the village
who knows of what awaits beyond the grave.
A grim topic for a bride-to-be.
It is a bride I fear,
which is why I must know:
Can the living marry the dead?
What on earth are you
speaking about?
Please, it's Victor.
He's married to a corpse.
He has a corpse bride!
There must be some way
to undo what's been done.
Hmm.
I believe I know
the thing to do.
Come with me.
Victoria?
Where are your corsets?
She's speaking in tongues.
Of unholy alliances.
Her mind has come
undone, I fear.
It's not true! Let me go!
Let me go!
Thank you, Pastor Galswells.
Thank you so very much.
Take her to her room!
No, I'm telling the truth.
Victor needs my help.
Hildegarde, you believe
me, don't you?
- Mother, Father, please.
- Seal the doors...
and bar the windows. See to it
that she doesn't escape again.
He needs our help! Oh, let me go!
Let me go!
Will the mortification
never cease?
It will be years before we can
show ourselves in public again.
What shall we do?
We shall continue as planned,
with or without Vincent.
- Victor.
- Whatever.
For that boy to toss aside a young
woman like Victoria...
it's positively criminal.
Why, if I had a woman
like your daughter on my arm...
I would lavish her with riches
befitting royalty.
Your lady wife
is a most fortunate woman.
Alas, I am not married.
I was betrothed
some years ago...
but tragedy snatched
my young bride away.
When one lives alone,
wealth counts for naught.
Oh.
Marvelous news, Victoria,
there'll be a wedding after all.
You found him?
Make haste, my dear, our relatives
will arrive at any moment.
We must have you looking
presentable for Lord Barkis.
Lord Barkis?
He will make a fine husband.
Aye. A fortuitous turn
of events indeed.
A far better prospect this time.
But I do not love him.
You cannot make me do this.
- We must.
- Please, I beg of you.
There must be another way.
Without your marriage
to Lord Barkis...
we shall be forced,
penniless, into the street.
We are destitute.
But Victor...
Victor Van Dort has gone, child.
You shall marry Lord
Barkis tomorrow.
- According to plan.
Oh, my dear. Oh, don't
look at me that way.
You have only to suffer this
union until death do us part.
And that will come
sooner than you think.
Oh, it's almost dawn!
Where could he be?
Victor Van Dort
elopes with corpse!
Heartbroken bride to wed
wealthy newcomer!
Wealthy newcomer? It cannot be.
Did he say corpse?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
What corpse would marry our Victor?
Oh, Mayhew!
Silence that blasted coughing.
Mayhew, are you
trying to kill us?
I think he's trying to kill us.
I...
think you dropped this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lied to you
about wanting to see my parents.
It's just this whole day
hasn't gone quite, well...
according to plan.
Pardon my enthusiasm.
I like your enthusiasm.
- New arrival! New arrival!
- Lights up!
Hurry up, boys! Vite, vite.
Bonjour! Bienvenue!
Drinks for everyone.
Another pint, sir?
- No, no. Just a half.
It is impossible to get
good help anymore.
Welcoming committee, coming through!
Coming through!
- My name's Plum. Miss Plum.
- Mayhew?
Mayhew! How nice to see...
I'm so sorry.
Oh, yeah. Actually,
though, I feel great.
Hurry up, boys. Can you not
see the gentleman is parched?
Mayhew, I have to get back.
They all must be worried sick.
How is everyone?
Well, they're still wondering
where you slipped off to.
Oh, and Miss Victoria...
Yes? Yes, how is she?
Well, she's getting
married this evening.
What? Married to who?
Some newcomer, Lord
Somebody-or-Other.
But that's impossible!
Yeah, with you gone and all...
I guess they didn't
wanna waste the cake.
But how could she?
Women, you can't live with them.
You can't live with... Hiccup!
Time to pick up the pieces and...
You know, and move on, I suppose.
Speaking of picking
up the pieces?
Victor? Where are you going?
Miss Victoria, we must
leave for the church now.
Yesterday I thought
my wedding would be happy.
Now I feel like I'm caught
in the tide, pulled out to sea.
The sea leads
to many places, dearie.
Maybe you'll land
somewhere better.
With this candle, I will light
your way in darkness.
With this ring, I ask
you to be mine.
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
Oh, oh, dear.
I'm too late.
Oh, Mrs. Plum, what am I to do?
He just walked off without saying a word.
Are all men like this?
Well, I'm afraid none of them
are very bright.
They get something stuck
in their heads...
and you can't do
a thing with them.
My dear, we have to talk.
Let me tell her, please.
Let me tell her.
- Heh, heh, heh.
- What?
There is a complication
with your marriage.
I don't understand.
The vows are binding
only until death do you part.
What are you saying?
Death has already parted you.
If he finds out, he'll leave.
There must be
something you can do.
Well, there is one way.
Oh, please, please,
let me tell her.
It requires
the greatest sacrifice.
- Go on, get to the good part.
- What is it?
- We have to kill him!
- What?
Victor would have to give
up the life he had forever.
He would need to repeat his vows
in the land of the living...
and drink from the wine of ages.
Poison!
This would stop
his heart forever.
Only then would he be
free to give it to you.
I could never ask him.
You don't have to.
I'll do it.
My boy, if you
choose this path...
you may never return
to the world above.
Do you understand?
I do.
Gather round.
Gather round, everybody.
We've decided to do
this thing properly.
So grab what you
can and follow us.
We're moving this
wedding party upstairs.
Upstairs? I didn't know
we had an upstairs.
- Sounds creepy.
- Let's go!
A wedding, a wedding We're
going to have a wedding.
Hold on, Victor.
You can't get married
looking like that.
The spiders think you're very cute
But goodness knows you need a suit.
But have no fears, we're quite adept
We'll have you looking lovely, lovely.
Lovely, lovely, lovely,
lovely, lovely yet.
A little stitch, a little tuck
Some tender loving care.
A little thread will fix you up And
we've got plenty as you see.
And personally guarantee
Our quality repairs.
A little here, I'll fix the mess
We're going to do our very best.
When everybody sees you They
will all be quite impressed.
They will all be
quite impressed.
A wedding, we're going to have.
A wedding cake is no mistake
It must be quite sublime.
- We're missing something.
- Try some dust.
I wish I had more time.
Perhaps there's something I can
do These bones might help a bit.
- Oh, my nose.
- Sorry.
Wait a minute, that's it.
- A little of that.
- A little of this.
The perfect cake
is hard to miss.
A wedding, a wedding
We're going to have.
A wedding.
Huzzah, huzzah.
We're going to have
a wedding A wedding.
Let's all give out a cheer 'cause
The bride is getting married today.
Hurray!
One thing you can surely say
Is we will stand beside.
Until the end we will defend
Our one and only bride.
Our bride-to-be, our bride-to-be
Our lovely Corpse Bride.
Huzzah! Hooray! Huzzah! Hooray!
Our bride is getting
married today.
- Oh, there she is.
- Here she comes.
Oh, oh, the bride is here.
She's waited for this
day For many a year.
For this day, for this day
Our hopes and our pride.
The bride is here
Here comes the bride.
Here comes the bride
For this day, for this
day Will last forever.
And all of her friends
Will work together.
To make it the perfect day
She's always dreamed.
Our hopes and our pride Our
bride, our lovely bride.
We're going to have a party
Like nobody's ever seen.
The living in the land above Will
not know where they've been.
The land above The
party of the bride.
Here comes the bride On
this glorious day of days.
Up to the land of the living.
To celebrate.
Oh, dear.
Quiet down now, everyone.
Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Elegant, cultured, radiant.
Victoria has found a husband...
with all these
qualities and more.
Serendipity brought
us together...
and no force on earth
could tear us apart.
Oh!
Mm?
There's an eye in me soup.
- Ooooh!
- Oh! Oh!
Aaah!
Oh, sorry.
Fetch me musket!
Fetch your own musket. I'm off!
Coming through. Coming through.
Excuse me, you don't know me,
but I used to live in your dead mother.
Hey, hold on there.
I love a woman with meat on her bones.
Heh, heh, heh.
Finis, who invited these people?
They must be from your side
of the family.
Certainly not.
Why, if my Grandfather Everglot could
see this, he'd be turning in his grave.
Finis.
Where do you keep the spirits?
In other news...
the dead walk the earth!
Get back! Don't try
and sneak up on me!
Get back!
I'll give you such a wallop.
No.
Yeah.
Grandpa?
Aww...
Huh?
- Bounder!
- Sweetie pie.
- Monster.
- Buttercup.
- Cad!
- Gertrude!
Alfred?
Oh?
You've been dead for 15 years.
Frankly, my dear,
I don't give a damn.
Ethel!
Wait. That's it.
We're going to take whatever money
we can and get out of here.
Money? What money?
Your dowry. It's my right!
But my parents don't
have any money.
It's my marriage to you
that will save them from the poorhouse.
Th... The poorhouse?
You're lying. It isn't true.
Tell me that you're lying!
Did things not go according
to your plan, Lord Barkis?
Well, perhaps in disappointment
we are perfectly matched.
Be gone, ye demons from hell!
Back to the void
from whence you came!
You shall not enter here.
Back, back!
Keep it down, we're in a church.
Evening.
Dearly beloved and departed...
we are gathered here today to join
this man and this corpse in marriage.
- Victor?
- Shh!
Living first.
With this hand...
I will lift your sorrows.
Your cup will never empty...
for I will be your wine.
Now you.
With this hand...
I will lift your sorrows.
Your cup will never empty.
For I will be...
I will be...
Go on, my dear.
Your cup...
will never empty...
for I will be...
I will be your wine.
She's having second thoughts.
I can't.
What's wrong?
This is wrong.
I was a bride.
My dreams were taken from me.
Well, now...
Now I've stolen them
from someone else.
I love you, Victor.
But you're not mine.
Victoria!
Oh, how touching.
I always cry at weddings.
Our young lovers
together at last.
Surely now they can live
happily ever after.
But you forget...
she's still my wife!
I'll not leave
here empty-handed!
You?
Emily?
You!
But... But... I left you.
For dead.
This woman is obviously
delusional!
Sorry to cut things short,
but we must be on our way.
Take your hands off her.
Do I have to kill you too?
Aargh!
Victor, catch!
Sorry.
Ah, sacrebleu!
I say, you're not
playing fair, sir.
Touché, my dear.
Get out.
Oh, I'm leaving.
But first a toast. To Emily.
Always the bridesmaid,
never the bride.
Tell me, my dear...
can a heart still break once
it's stopped beating? Hm?
Let me at him!
- No, don't hold me back.
- Wait.
We must abide by their rules.
We are amongst the living.
Well said.
Ah!
Not anymore.
Yep, you're right.
He's all yours.
New arrival.
Oh, Victor, I never thought
I'd see you again.
Wait.
I made a promise.
You kept your promise.
You set me free.
Now I can do the same for you.
Subtitles by SDI Media Group